[left hand] grasp the blue block | [right hand] grasp the green block | [both hands] place the blue and green blocks side by side on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the red block | [left hand] hold the blue and green blocks | [right hand] place the red block on top of the blue and green blocks | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the purple block | [right hand] grasp the green block | [left hand] place the purple block on the stack | [right hand] place the green block on the stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the yellow block | [right hand] hold the green block | [left hand] place the yellow block on the stack | [right hand] place the green block on the stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the purple block | [right hand] grasp the white block | [left hand] place the purple block on the stack | [right hand] place the white block on the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the red block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the red block on top of the stack | [right hand] grasp another red block | [right hand] place the red block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the green block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the green block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] grasp the purple block | [left hand] place the green block on the table | [right hand] place the purple block on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the purple block | [left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] place the purple block on top of the stack | [left hand] place the green block on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the yellow block | [left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] place the yellow block on top of the stack | [left hand] place the green block on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the white block | [left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] place the white block on top of the stack | [left hand] place the green block on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the blue block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the blue block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the gray block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the gray block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the yellow block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the yellow block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the blue block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the blue block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the gray block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the gray block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the yellow block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the yellow block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the blue block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the blue block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the white block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the white block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the green block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the green block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] grasp the light blue block | [left hand] hold the stack | [right hand] place the light blue block on top of the stack | [ego] stay still